Hi. Christy.
- Hey, Leonard.
- I'm Sheldon.
(Christie:)Right. You're Howard's entourage.
So, Christy, what are your plans?
(Christie:)Well, Howard said he'd take me shopping
in Beverly Hills.
(Penny:)Yeah, no, I meant plans to find
someplace to live other than with me.
(Penny:)Not that I don't love having you,
but it's a little crowded.
(Leonard:)Penny, you're always welcome
to stay with us.
(Sheldon:)Oh, terrific.
Now we're running a cute little B & B.
Let me offer a little thinking here.
- Why doesn't Christy stay with me?
- You live with your mother.
(Howard:)I do not. My mother lives with me.
It's settled. Christy will stay with Howard,
Penny can go back to her apartment.
(Sheldon:)And I'll watch the last 24 minutes
of Doctor Who...
(Sheldon:)...although at this point,
it's more like Doctor Why Bother?
- Sheldon, you just can't dictate...
- No more talking. Everybody go.
So, what do you say?
Wanna repair to Casa Wolowitz?
(Christie:)What is that, like a Mexican deli?